www.tvsubtitles.net
"From this time
until the end of time,
we are the free and independent
Kingdom of the North."
You'll give the Starks
our reply, cousin?
I will, Your Grace.
Did you see my brother when you
were the Starks' guest?
I did.
Tell him he's not
been forgotten.
( Grunts )
( Panting )
I'll do it.
Come, brothers.
We'll leave him to it.
Be quick about it.
- ( Grunts )
- ( Sword clangs )
I've yielded Winterfell
to Prince Theon.
All of you should do
as he commands.
Betray me and you will
wish you hadn't.
Man:
All hail the king.
- ( Groans )
- ( Crowd murmuring )
- Who threw that?
- ( Crowd shouting )
Get back!
( Whimpering )
You're all right now, little bird.
You're all right.
Your brothers desert you?
- We'll stop here.
- Think they're out looking for you?
Yes.
( Grunts )
What might this be?
Let's go.
Amory Lorch.
Now!
A man will do
what must be done.
Guard!
I have something for you
from Prince Theon.
( Gurgles )
When I came to this city,
I had nothing.
Today I am the richest
man in Qarth
with no regrets.
Where are they?
Where are my dragons?!
( Screeching )
( Theme music playing )
♪ Game of Thrones 2x07 ♪
A Man Without Honor
Original Air Date on May 13, 2012
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
♪
A cripple?
You let a cripple escape?
The boy can't walk,
but somehow
he slipped past you?
The giant must have
took him.
The giant?
Hodor?
Oh, well,
that's all right, then.
You let a halfwit
escape with a cripple.
And Rickon, too?
The little one?
Gone along with
the wildling woman,
the one you were fucking.
( Grunting )
( Man groaning )
( Panting )
Right, get the horses
and the hounds.
- ( Dogs barking )
- Come on, find the scent.
Come on,
where they going?
Halt!
Enjoying
your first hunt?
So far, hunting seems very similar
to riding, My Lord.
With hunting,
there's blood at the end.
They're little boys.
I was a little boy
when I was torn away from
my home and brought here.
So I kept my word.
I never ran away.
If I find them soon enough,
I won't hurt them.
Well, I'll hurt them,
but I won't kill them.
Those boys are of far more value
to you alive than dead.
They have no value
to me missing.
Robb will have sent a force
to retake Winterfell by now.
Robb's in the Riverlands.
My sister's in Deepwood Motte.
She'll get here
long before they do.
And Ned Stark always
said 500 men could hold
Winterfell against 10,000.
- ( Dogs barking )
- Man: We have a scent!
The hounds have the scent.
Come, Maester,
don't look so grim.
It's all just a game.
Osha: We should have
took more food.
We couldn't risk
going to the kitchens.
Those people
all love you.
They would have given
you whatever you needed.
And if Theon found out,
he'd hang them.
- The boy can't survive on walnuts.
- I'm fine.
We've been walking
since before sunrise.
- Even Hodor will tire.
- Hodor.
- Even you, sweet giant.
- ( Chuckles ) Hodor.
( Children shouting )
Wait, I know that farm.
I sent those two
Winterfell orphans there.
Jack and Billy.
They'll give us some food.
We can't risk it.
If Theon tracks us here,
he'll torture them
until he finds out
where we are.
Billy climbs a tree
better than anyone.
You've never seen me
climb a tree, little man.
They'll be after us
with hounds.
We got a good start
on them,
but we can't outrun
hounds forever.
Did you pull a knife
on me in the night?
What's the matter?
Can't be the first time
you pressed your bone
against a woman's ass.
Let's move.
Oh, it is
the first time.
How old are you, boy?
I'm a man
of the Night's Watch.
You're a boy who's
never been with a girl.
Don't your stones
start to hurt
if your bone
never gets--
Don't call them that.
What, stones?
Or bone?
Neither.
Both.
Move!
Ygritte: I heard they get
all swollen
and bruised if you
don't use them.
Of course, maybe that's
just what the lads say
when they want me
feeling sorry for them.
As if I'd feel
sorry for them.
Are there
no girl crows?
There are no women
of the Night's Watch, no.
So the lads just do it
with each other?
No.
- Never?
- Never.
We swore an oath.
You have sheep
at the Wall?
With your hands, then?
No wonder
you're all so miserable.
Would you please shut up?
( Mocking )
You think you're
better than me, crow.
- I'm a free woman--
- You're a free woman?
I might be your prisoner,
but I'm a free woman.
If you're my prisoner,
you're not a free woman.
That's what
"prisoner" means.
And you think you're free?
You swore
some stupid oath
and now you can never
touch a girl.
It was my choice
to say the words.
- So you don't like girls?
- Of course I like girls.
But you chose
never to touch them.
That's the price you pay if you want
to be a man of the Night's Watch.
So instead of getting
naked with a girl,
you'd prefer
to invade our lands--
Invade your lands?
Wildlings raid
our lands all the time.
Some of them tried to kill my
little brother, a crippled boy!
They're not your lands!
We've been here
the whole time.
You lot came along
and just put up a big wall
and said it was yours.
My father was Ned Stark.
I have the blood
of the First Men.
My ancestors lived here,
same as yours.
So why are you
fighting us?
Go on.
Now I want you
to tell me what happened.
- Guard: Come on, this way.
- ( Man screaming )
Come on, speak up.
Speak up.
( Sniffs )
Wolfsbane--
a rare substance.
This is no common assassin.
We hanged 20 men
last night.
I don't care
if you hanged 100.
A man tried to kill me.
I want his name
and I want his head.
Mountain: We think it was
an infiltrator
from the Brotherhood
Without Banners.
Pretentious name
for a band of outlaws.
We can't allow rebels
behind our lines
to harass us
with impunity.
We look like fools
and they look like heroes.
That's how kings fall.
I want them dead,
every one.
Killing them
isn't the problem.
It's finding them.
Have you gone soft,
Clegane?
I always thought you had
a talent for violence.
Burn the villages,
burn the farms.
Let them know what it means
to choose the wrong side.
Mmm.
Is that mutton?
Yes, My Lord.
Don't like mutton.
I'll bring
something else.
Leave it.
- Are you hungry?
- No.
Of course you are.
Eat.
I'll eat
in the kitchen later.
It's bad manners
to refuse a Lord's offer.
Sit.
Eat.
You're small for your age.
I suppose you've been
underfed your whole life.
I eat a lot.
- I just don't grow.
- Hmm.
This will be my last war,
win or lose.
Have you ever
lost before?
Do you think I'd be in my position
if I had lost a war?
But this is the one
I'll be remembered for.
The "War of Five Kings"
they're calling it.
My legacy will be determined
in the coming months.
Do you know
what legacy means?
It's what you pass down
to your children
and your children's
children.
It's what remains of you
when you're gone.
Harren the Black thought this castle
would be his legacy.
The greatest fortress
ever built--
the tallest towers,
the strongest walls.
The Great Hall
had 35 hearths.
35. Can you imagine?
Look at it now--
a blasted ruin.
Do you know
what happened?
Dragons?
Yes, dragons happened.
Harrenhal was built to withstand
an attack from the land.
A million men could have marched
on these walls
and a million men
would have been repelled.
But an attack from the air
with dragon fire-- mm.
Harren and all his sons
roasted alive within these walls.
Aegon Targaryen
changed the rules.
That's why every child alive
still knows his name
300 years after his death.
Aegon and his sisters.
Mm?
It wasn't just Aegon
riding his dragon.
It was Rhaenys
and Visenya, too.
Correct.
A student of history,
are you?
Rhaenys rode Meraxes.
Visenya rode Vhagar.
I'm sure I knew that
when I was a boy.
Visenya Targaryen
was a great warrior.
She had a Valyrian steel sword
she called Dark Sister.
Hmm.
She's a heroine
of yours, I take it?
Aren't most girls
more interested
in the pretty maidens
from the songs?
Jonquil with the flowers
in her hair?
- Most girls are idiots.
- Ha!
You remind me
of my daughter.
Where did you learn
all this stuff
about Visenya and her
Valyrian Steel sword?
From my father.
He was a well-read
stonemason.
Can't say I've ever met
a literate stonemason.
Have you met many
stonemasons, My Lord?
Careful now, girl.
I enjoy you,
but be careful.
Take that back
to the kitchen.
Eat what you want.
And, girl.
M'lord.
Lowborn girls
say "M'lord,"
not "My Lord."
If you're going
to pose as a commoner,
you should do it
properly.
My mother served
Lady Dustin
for many years,
My Lord.
She taught me how to speak
proper-- properly.
You're too smart
for your own good.
- Has anyone told you that?
- Yes.
Go on.
I beg pardon, Ser.
I should have
come to you after
to thank you
for saving me.
- You were so brave.
- Brave?
A dog doesn't need courage
to chase off rats.
Does it give you joy
to scare people?
No. It gives me joy
to kill people.
Spare me.
You can't tell me
Lord Eddard Stark of Winterfell
never killed a man.
It was his duty.
He never liked it.
Is that what he told you?
He lied.
Killing is the sweetest
thing there is.
Why are you always
so hateful?
You'll be glad
of the hateful things I do
someday when you're queen
and I'm all that stands
between you
and your beloved king.
I've demanded a meeting
of the Thirteen.
One of them did this
or knows who did.
You are one
of the Thirteen.
If I wanted your dragons,
I would have taken them.
- They mean nothing to me on their own.
- Nothing?
They're more valuable
than anything in the world.
Shall we look inside my vault and see
what selling your dragons
would buy me
I cannot buy already?
We will get them back.
There is no we,
so why would you help me
get them back?
I took you
under my protection
in front of the rulers
of my city.
A man is what others
say he is and no more.
If they say that
Xaro Xhoan Daxos is a liar,
my word is worth nothing.
I cannot let this thing
happen to you under my roof.
But it did happen
under your roof.
Khaleesi, many times
in my life I have been--
I don't care
where you've been.
You think we're savages because
we don't live in stone castles.
We can't make steel as good
as yours, it's true, but...
We're free.
If someone tried to tell us
we couldn't lie down
as man and woman,
we'd shove a spear
up his ass.
We don't go serving
some shit king
who's only king
because his father was.
No. No, you serve
Mance Rayder,
the King-Beyond-the-Wall.
We chose Mance Rayder
to lead us.
He was a crow,
same as you,
but he wanted
to be free.
You could be free, too.
You don't need to live
your whole life
taking commands
from old men.
Wake up when you want
to wake up.
I could show you the streams
to fish, the woods to hunt.
Build yourself a cabin and find
a woman to lie with in the night.
You're a pretty lad.
The girls would claw each other's
eyes out to get naked with you.
Walk.
I could teach you
how to do it.
I know how to do it.
You know nothing,
Jon Snow.
( Chatter )
And what did she say?
She admired your spirit,
Your Grace.
And what then?
She, uh...
If every man
were held accountable
for the actions
of every distant relative,
Ser Alton, we'd all hang.
She tore the paper
in half, Your Grace.
You've acted with honor.
I thank you for it.
Lord Karstark, see that
Ser Alton's pen is clean.
And give him a hot supper.
Ser Alton's pen
is occupied, Your Grace.
The prisoners
from the Yellow Fork.
Too many prisoners.
Is there room
for Ser Alton?
Does he need
to lie down?
Have the men
build him a new pen.
Put him in with
the Kingslayer for now.
Have your boy
watch over them.
Torrhen.
That will be all.
Your Grace.
A minute of your time?
I've been treating
your wounded men.
And my enemies
as some of my bannermen
are fond of mentioning.
They're not my enemies.
That's what I tell
my bannermen.
I've already run through the
supplies I brought with me.
Some are easily replaced--
egg yolks, turpentine,
oil of roses.
But some are not.
I need silk
for stitching.
I need fennel root
for those with fever, willow bark.
Mostly I need
milk of the poppy.
You saw what it was like
to amputate a foot without any.
I assume there will be
more loss of limb before
this war is over.
- If you need help finding these--
- I know where to find them.
I'm sorry, I shouldn't
interrupt you.
Continue, My Lady.
You're riding to the Crag
to negotiate a surrender?
Yes.
The Crag will have a Maester
and he will have what I need.
I expect he will.
If I could write a list--
come with me
to the Crag.
I don't think
that will be--
Let the Maester
show you his stores.
I want the wounded men
to be treated well--
all the wounded men.
( Dog barking )
Woman:
Children, come inside, quick.
Hurry up!
- ( Dog barking )
- Man: Can't find anything, Ser.
- They've lost the scent.
- Try again.
We've circled
this farmhouse twice.
There's no sign of them.
We could start the search fresh
in the morning, My Lord.
I'm looking at spending
the rest of life
being treated like a fool and
a eunuch by my own people.
Ask yourself, "Is there anything
I wouldn't do
to stop that
from happening?"
The hounds will find
the scent again.
I'll beat them
until they do.
I'll whip every man here
until I have
both those boys in hand.
And once I've got them,
the pampered little shits...
It's better to be
cruel than weak.
Prince Theon.
- Where are they?
- Who, m'lord?
The Stark boys.
Where are they?
I don't know.
I seen no one.
Oh!
Think harder.
I swear, m'lord,
I don't know.
My Lord, over here.
I think I've found
what we're looking for.
Send the old man home.
Go back to Winterfell.
Take him back.
Theon, don't do this.
( Birds chirping )
You came back.
As soon as I heard.
Do you know anything?
- Irri is dead.
- I know.
- She was a good--
- she's dead.
She died alone.
She died for me
and I couldn't protect her.
Doreah?
We can't find her.
She must be dead, too.
I led my people
out of the Red Waste
and into
the slaughterhouse.
I should have been here.
You went to find me
a ship.
My place is by your side.
I shouldn't have left you
alone with these people.
These people?
They are not
to be trusted.
And who is to be trusted?
Who are my people?
The Targaryens?
I only knew one--
my brother,
and he would have let
1,000 men rape me
if it had got him
the crown.
The Dothraki?
Most of them turned on me
the day that Khal Drogo
fell from his horse.
Your people
are in Westeros.
The people in Westeros
don't know I'm alive.
- They will soon enough.
- And then what?
They'll pray for my return?
They'll wave dragon banners
and shout my name?
That's what my brother believed
and he was a fool.
You are not your brother.
Trust me, Khaleesi.
There it is--
"trust me."
And it's you I should trust,
Ser Jorah?
Only you?
I don't need trust
any longer.
I don't want it and I don't have
room for it.
You are too young
to be so--
And you are too familiar.
Forgive me, Khaleesi.
No one can survive
in this world without help.
No one.
Let me help you, please.
Tell me how.
Find my dragons.
Ygritte: How long till we get
back to your crows?
We're close.
What, a day?
A half-day?
You don't know, do you?
- Do you even know where they are?
- We're close.
What do you think they'll say
when they hear about you and me?
Nothing happened
between you and me.
"I swear it,
old master king crow, Ser,
we were only close
together for warmth.
And then I felt it,
right up against
me backside like a club.
I can show you the bruise
on me tailbone.
And before I knew
what was where, his-- his--
well, it was all out in the open,
all angry as you like.
And I didn't want to want it,
but, oh, I did!
And he spread me legs
and-- ruined.
The shame of it.
Now I can never marry
a perfumed lord.
What will me poor
savage father say?"
Turn back around.
"And I thought that we were done,
but he said,
( deep voice )
'Turn back around.'"
( normal voice )
I'll tell you what, Jon Snow,
since it's going to be
your word against mine,
and since you can't talk
about it without blushing,
we may as well just.
What, right here
in the muck?
I'll keep you
warm enough.
Are you that afraid
of it?
That's enough.
Oh, it's nice
and wet and warm.
Enough
it don't have teeth.
All right!
All right.
Gods, you're dull.
( Grunting )
( Sword rings )
( Ygritte whistles )
Should have took me
while you had the chance.
( Sansa crying )
No, no!
- ( Screams )
- ( Laughs )
( Screams )
No. Oh, no.
( Whimpering )
It's all right.
Give me that.
If the queen sees I can have
Joffrey's children now...
Help me flip it over.
- Where are you going?
- To tell her Grace.
You'll say nothing
to anyone.
Do you understand?
Your mother might have
prepared you.
You flowered, my dear.
No more.
My mother told me, but I
thought it would be different.
In what way?
I thought
it would be less--
less messy.
Wait until you bear
the child.
You're a woman now.
Do you have any idea
what that means?
I'm fit to bear children
for the king?
A prospect that
once delighted you--
bringing little princes
and princesses into the world,
the greatest honor
for a queen.
Joffrey has always
been difficult.
Even his birth,
I labored a day and a half
to bring him
into this world.
You cannot imagine
the pain.
I screamed so loudly,
I was sure
Robert would hear me
in the Kingswood.
His Grace was not
with you?
Robert was hunting.
That was his custom.
Whenever my time was near,
my royal husband
would flee to the trees
with his huntsmen
and his hounds.
And when he returned,
he would present me
with some pelts
or a stag's head,
and I would present him
with a baby.
Not that I wanted
him there, mind you.
I had Grand Maester Pycelle,
an army of midwives,
and I had my brother.
When they told Jaime he wasn't
allowed in the birthing room,
he smiled and asked
which one of them
proposed to keep him out.
Joffrey will show you
no such devotion.
You may never
love the king,
but you will love
his children.
I love his Grace
with all my heart.
That's so very
touching to hear.
Permit me to share
some womanly wisdom with you
on this very special day.
The more people you love,
the weaker you are.
You'll do things for them that
you know you shouldn't do.
You'll act the fool to make them
happy, to keep them safe.
Love no one
but your children.
On that front,
a mother has no choice.
But... shouldn't
I love Joffrey, Your Grace?
You can try,
little dove.
( Chatter )
Who did you say
your mother was again?
Cinda Lannister.
Is she the fat one?
Well, perhaps she's gotten
a little larger than she--
No, no. There's only one
fat Lannister.
If she was your mother,
you'd know it.
I-- I squired
for you once, you know?
When?
The tournament the day
of Willem Frey's wedding.
I went to
Willem Frey's wedding?
You did.
Your squire had gotten
so drunk the night before that he--
He threw up on his horse
on the way
to the tourney grounds.
- What was his name?
- Bryan.
( Laughs )
Poor lad.
That was my brother's doing,
I seem to recall.
I remember you.
You had never squired
for anyone before.
That's right.
I ran up and volunteered.
"Let me, My Lord.
Let me."
My father was furious,
afraid I'd embarrass
our family
in front of the family.
You didn't, though.
- You really remember?
- Mm.
You knew when you were needed
and when to go away.
It's a rare talent.
Most of my squires,
they mean well,
but young men with big jobs,
they tend to overdo them.
Well, when I think
back to that day--
( hisses )
You were saying?
I--
never mind.
It's embarrassing.
More embarrassing
than being chained to a post
covered in your own shit?
I remember everything
about that day--
your helmet, your horse,
the rake line in the dirt
along the list,
where the sun was
in the sky
when you knocked
Balon Swann from his horse,
and the dent in your shield
when you handed it back to me.
I'll remember it all
until I die.
That was the best day
of my life.
And I remember being on the field
after it was over.
All the competitors
were done.
I was the last one
out there.
And I couldn't leave.
I couldn't bring myself
to go and sit with my family
at a table so far
on the edge of the feast
you could barely
even see the bride.
And I couldn't bear to tell them
what it had been like squiring for you
when I knew that they could
never have the faintest idea
what I was talking about.
I understand completely.
How could you?
S-sorry, I-- I didn't
mean to doubt you.
- It's just that I--
- I was 16 once.
I also had to replace someone's
squire on short notice.
Which knight was it?
Barristan Selmy.
The fight against
the Kingswood outlaws.
Before your time.
What was he like?
( Sighs )
He was
a painter,
a painter
who only used red.
I couldn't imagine being
able to fight like that,
not back then.
And to help him do that,
to be a part of something
that perfect...
I don't need to explain
how that felt, not to you.
It's hard to put
into words.
It's like stepping
into a dream
you've been dreaming
for as long as you can remember
and finding out
that the dream
is more real
than your life.
Leaving
that battlefield was
like being dragged off
to prison.
- Did you squire for him again?
- No.
I didn't have your gift.
He couldn't take a step
without stepping on me.
I was awful,
a complete liability...
until one of the outlaws
decided to take on
a 16-year-old squire.
It's a good thing
I am who I am.
( Chuckles ) I'd have been useless
at anything else.
I'm not well-suited
for imprisonment.
Shocking, I know.
Some men are.
Ned Stark--
I imagine he made
an excellent prisoner
right up until the end.
But me, though--
my life has left me
uniquely unfit
for constraint.
Have you thought about...?
Of course.
- Every day.
- And?
Good prisoners breed
good jailers, apparently.
The Starks
are very careful.
But there is a way,
I think.
It wasn't possible
until now.
What is it?
- It's actually quite simple.
- Well, let me help you.
You'll only have
to do one thing.
Tell me.
You'll have to die.
( Crunching )
( Choking )
( Bone breaks )
( Bird screeching )
Jorah the Andal.
This man must sail
past old Valyria.
All who travel too close to
the Doom must have protection.
I didn't come here
for lessons.
No, you came
for the dragons.
You have them?
Where are they?
Draw your sword.
See what your steel
is worth.
You want to please
the Mother of Dragons.
You love her.
Where are the dragons?
Will you betray her again,
Jorah the Andal?
Will you betray her again?
Never.
The thief you seek
is with her now.
Spice King: I did not leave
the comfort of my home
to come to yours
and be called a thief.
No one is calling you
a thief.
Who is she to accuse us?
Please,
they're my children.
- I'm begging you.
- Begging us?
It wasn't very long ago
you were threatening us.
Without me,
the dragons will die.
It will be
for the best.
Your dragons
will bring the world
nothing but death
and misery, my dear.
If I knew where they were,
I would not tell you.
Pyat Pree:
You are cruel, my friend.
The mother of dragons
is in the right.
She must be reunited
with her babies.
- I will help you, Khaleesi.
- How?
I will take you
to the House of the Undying
where I have put them.
You have my dragons?
When I learned you were
coming to our city,
I made an arrangement
with the King of Qarth.
( Laughter )
He procured them for me.
- But there is no King of Qarth.
- Xaro: There is now.
That was the other half
of the arrangement.
You would keep your gates
and your minds closed
to everything
outside your walls,
but Qarth cannot remain
the greatest city that ever was
if it refuses to change.
I will open Qarth
to the world
as I have forced it
to open itself to me.
Your ambition
is an inspiration.
But like all upstarts,
you overreach.
Three dragons
the size of cats
and an alliance
with a charlatan
do not make you a king.
An upstart
and a charlatan?
Empires have been
built by less.
Those on the margins
often come to control the center,
and those in the center
make room for them,
willingly or otherwise.
The Mother of Dragons
will be with her babies.
She will give them
her love
and they will thrive
by her side...
forever.
A mother should be
with her children.
Where will you run to,
Daenerys Stormborn?
Your dragons wait for you
in the House of the Undying.
Come see them.
- Lady Stark!
- No farther.
Keep your hands
off me, woman.
Don't enter without
an invitation, man.
Forgive me.
Lady Stark.
- Catelyn: What is it?
- They caught the Kingslayer.
( Men shouting )
- Kill the fucking Kingslayer!
- Hang him!
( Men shouting )
You'll die today.
Justice for
the Karstark.
Gut him!
Get back!
I want his head!
Any man who stands
between a father
and his vengeance
asks for death.
Lord Karstark,
this man
is our prisoner.
This monster
killed my son.
And crippled mine.
He will answer
for his crimes,
I promise you,
but not here.
I will have his head.
And if you try and stop me--
You will strike me down?
Have you forgotten me, Ser?
I am the widow of your
liege Lord Eddark Stark.
I am the mother
of your king!
- And where is our king now?
- You know very well.
He has gone to the Crag
to accept the surrender.
Aye, gone to the Crag,
but not to negotiate.
He brought that
foreign bitch with him.
How dare you?
Threatening My Lady
is an act of treason.
Treason?
How can it be treason
to kill Lannisters?
I understand
your grief, My Lord--
better than most
I understand it--
but in the name of my son,
the King in the North,
stand down.
When your son returns,
I will demand
this murderer's head.
Wise men do not
make demands of kings.
Fathers who love
their sons do.
I will have his head.
Thank you for fighting
on my behalf, Lady Stark.
I would have come
to your defense, but--
Take him to the stockades.
Bind him with every chain
you can find!
You've become a real she-wolf
in your later years.
There's not much fish
left in you.
And gag him!
Since when do you light
your own candles?
Since I decided that
I can't stand to look
at any of my handmaidens
for another instant.
How many times can you
read one raven scroll?
Stannis Baratheon's fleet
has been spotted sailing north
past Tarth-- 200 ships.
- More than we have.
- Yes, that's more than we have.
He'll be at our gates
within five days,
four if he has the wind.
We have strong,
high walls.
We'll rain fire
down on them from above.
"Rain fire on them
from above."
You're quoting father,
aren't you?
Why not?
He has a good mind
for strategy, doesn't he?
We call it tactics,
not strategy.
But, yes, he does have
a good mind for it.
The best mind,
some would say.
Sadly, he's not here.
It's just you,
me, and Joffrey,
the Lord
of the Seven Kingdoms
and protector of the realm.
I'm sure you'll make
a point eventually.
He needs to start
acting like a king.
This war you started
is coming to our doorstep.
And if the entire city
wants Joffrey dead--
I'm not the one giving
the boy whores to abuse.
I thought the girls
might help him.
- Did you?
- I was wrong.
If we can't
control him...
Do you think
I haven't tried?
He doesn't listen to me.
It's hard to put
a leash on a dog
once you've put
a crown on its head.
I always hoped
he'd be like Jaime.
He looks like him...
in a certain light.
The boy is more
Robert than Jaime.
Robert was a drunken fool,
but he didn't enjoy cruelty.
Sometimes I wonder...
What?
If this is the price
for what we've done,
for our sins.
Sins?
The Targaryens--
Wed brother and sister
for hundreds of years,
I know.
That's what Jaime and I would say to
each other in our moments of doubt.
It's what I told Ned Stark when he
was stupid enough to confront me.
Half the Targaryens
went mad, didn't they?
What's the saying?
Every time a Targaryen is born,
the Gods flip a coin.
You've beaten the odds.
Tommen and Myrcella
are good, decent children,
both of them.
( Crying )
- Why wait?
- We're sworn to the king.
- There's not a king.
- That's treason.
So is saving
Lannisters, yeah?
- Back off, you.
- No, I won't.
Your son returns
at dawn, My Lady?
So they say.
Brienne: The Kingslayer
won't last the night.
The more they drink,
the angrier they'll get.
And when the Karstarks
draw their swords...
who wants to die
defending a Lannister?
Come.
I need to be alone
with him.
- My Lady, our orders--
- your orders, which I just gave you,
are to leave me
alone with him.
Come to say goodbye,
Lady Stark?
I believe it's my last night
in this world.
Is that a woman?
Do you hear them
out there?
They want your head.
Well, old Lord Karstark
doesn't seem to like me.
You strangled his son
with your chains.
Oh, oh.
Was he the one
on guard duty?
( Sighs )
He was in my way.
Any Knight would have
done the same.
You are no Knight.
You have forsaken
every vow you ever took.
So many vows.
They make you swear
and swear.
Defend the king,
obey the king,
obey your father,
protect the innocent,
defend the weak.
But what if your father
despises the king?
What if the king
massacres the innocent?
It's too much.
No matter what you do,
you're forsaking one vow or another.
Where did you find
this beast?
She is a truer Knight
than you will ever be,
Kingslayer.
What a king he was.
Here's to Aerys Targaryen,
the second of his name,
Lord of the Seven Kingdoms,
Protector of the realm,
and to the sword
I shoved in his back.
You are a man
without honor.
Do you know
I've never been with
any woman but Cersei?
So in my own way,
I have more honor
than poor old dead Ned.
What was the name of that
bastard so in he fathered?
- Brienne.
- No, that wasn't it.
Snow, a bastard
from the North.
Now, when--
when good old Ned
came home with
some whore's baby,
did you pretend
to love it?
No. You're not very good
at pretending.
You're an honest woman.
You hated that boy,
didn't you?
How could you not
hate him?
The walking,
talking reminder
that the honorable
Lord Eddark Stark
fucked another woman.
Your sword.
I told you
what would happen.
All of you--
I told you what would happen
if you served me loyally...
and what would happen
if you did not.
What are you doing?
What have you done?
If there's any who still question
whether your new lord
means what he says...
Here is the answer
to your question.
( Crowd gasps, murmurs )
No!
( Theme music playing )
== sync, corrected by elderman ==